What smells so good
I provide food this week
Cooking now?
Hurry up
Go to the kitchen to help
Someone is cooking, who?
Why are you here
Look
Get a clean plate here
Your kitchen ventilator and recipe
So good, it's a waste to not use them
What, don't work in hotel now
Working as a nanny here?
Can you afford to hire me
No nonsense
Tell me
How did you piss off my father
Not feeling good right?
Just ask your father
Meal time
It's your favourite shirmps
Good
It's bought
Come, have a seat
You may not know each other
Introduce
This is Luo Yue
Who moved to our opposite house days ago
Neighbor
Opposite
This is the son I mentioned to you
Cheng Hao
You know each other
What a coincidence
T told you the other day
Gonna introduce my friend to you
The dating consultant
Is him
It's your son
Then it's easy
That
You come here
What
The meal today
Is a trap for me?
I don't want your life
I told my father my second job
Is taking my life
Follow me
What
Take a look, see
You father likes it
The middle on with white clothes
It most elegant
Aunt Yang
Was a teacher before
She is retired now
Her husband has passed away many years ago
Children are not by her side
Same as your father
Wait
I know what you are up to
So you want your son
To set up a date for his father
Unbelievable
Why are you so selfish?
It's not like
Getting yourself a step-mother
It's getting a companion
For your father
Save it
Ask yourself
Are you really doing it for him?
Wanna find troubles for me
It'ok, don't use my father as an excuse
Cheng Hao
I've been here for a month
Live right opposite your house
Why we didn't meet until today?
Because God doesn't want it
Because you seldom come back
To see your father
Have you thought that
From getting up to falling asleep
How did he spend his day?
He can't cook
How does he deal with food
He's old
Has no one to talk to
He finds a person
That he can live with
Nothing wrong about it
It sounds ok
But our situation is different
You're not gonna convince me
Since you refuse to help your father
Then leave me alone
It's my business to deal with aunt Yang
Bye
She is not the same type as my mother
Father
I'm leaving now
We'll talk later next week
Answer me
You gave up being a dentist
Now a dating consultant
You are wrong
I'm good at my work
You are outside all day long
It's not right
Why not right?
What I'm doing
Is just slash youth
If you have time, energy and skills
It's ok
Don't tell me this
You are a dentist
You rely on your techniques
Even if you fix shoes for people
I can understand it
But setting dates for others?
You are a matchmaker
And you are a male matchmaker
It's wrong
Matchmaker is superstitious
I'm study sexual relationship
And psychology
This is science, different
Bullshit
If it's science
Then in these years
Have you brought home a girl?
No, have you ever
Taken it seriously
You can't solve your own problem
Let alone being a consultant
Are you done
Not done
You don't understand my job
It's not so bad like you are saying
It is
I didn't solve my own problem
But how many couples
Have I brought together, do you know?
When it comes to love
Someone will never understand
Someone just knows it
Nothing to do with time and amount
You have been with my mother for decades
Did you make it work?
You don't understand my mother
Let alone women
She is gone
You can't let it go
Because you are guilty
Shut up
I don't need your comments
All right
What's wrong with man matchmaker
So long as I can help people
Then it's a good business
It's not a shame
And
You are so old
You go out each time
To find emotional sustenance
It's solving your problem
Then let's be clear
You and aunt Yang
I won't oppose
But I won't agree either
Make your own decision
Cheng Hao didn't piss you off yesterday?
All these years
It's me who schools him
It's his first time to
Be mad at me
Uncle Cheng, I didn't do it on purpose
I don't blame you
It's still our own business
And he seems doesn't agree
With me and Yang
Just forget it
Don't
You can't just give up for him
It's not right
7 days a week
168 hours
Cheng Hao stays at home for 3 hours
The rest 165 hours
You're all alone
What does he do every day
Working, meeting people. Having fun
How can he understand you
You don't need to care about him
You can finally find yourself a companion
Look after each other
How about I raising a dog
But I hate it
Dog is different
50 to 60 years old
Is life's second spring
You are retired finally
Don't have work's burden
Children are grown up
You can live for yourself now
Why need a dog
It's not easy
If you really think that way
Your mother remarried then
When you hid in Europe
I studied abroad alone
Because my mother remarried
I can plan for myself
Chinese parents always have
Bad relationship with their children
Because they always
Trapped by blood ties
Bearing unnecessary scarfice
Might as well live for yourself
That's right
Relly easy
It's easy to talk to you
I and Yang
Can reach the realm
I have thought of it
I tell you
We need
To understand Yang's interests
From different angles
We don't have dating consultant
It's ok
So long as we take time
It'll work
I see
Anyway Yang
What
Honestly
When did you hang out
With my father
What
You thought I moved here on purpose
Coincidence
What a coincidence
I'm saying
Can you be a bit positive
If I want to deal with you
I would move to the opposite of your house
You know what I can do
But I won't hurt innocents
You care so much about my father
What are you up to
When I knew he's your father
I giggled
I have one more card against you
But after I talked to him
I really want to find a step-mother for you
He's not easy
Step-mother for who
You don't know about us
He's not easy
He is just used to yell at my mother
He doesn't talk much
Because I'm not there
No one would take his abuse
He's not lonely
Are you old
Do you know what it feels like
To be alone
It's the biggest punishment for someone
To grow old alone
Do you think your father is a bad man?
What did it take
To get a life companion?
Health
If no accident occurs
You need to make sure
She's loyal
You are a dating consultant
You think
You believe in love
I believe in love
But don't believe people
All right
I will toast to you
I only drink martini
No martini
My mother
Miss Liu
Was a nurse
Took care of ICU patients
For years
She told me
One interesting pheonmenon
Some people recover drom comma
When they wake up
So long as she's women
The first question would be
Where is my children and husband, are they ok?
But if he's a man
You know what's the first question?
What
Throw the bedclothes back
Are you talking dirty?
It's real
So men are ok
So are women
Not enough when it's not good
Good
At least we agree something
In common
A breakthrough
Let's finish and leave
I'll help your father